[{"QN":"1","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is the first step in any Kanban Implementation","A":" Implement F/B loop","B":" Manage Flow","C":" Limit WIP","D":" Define explicit policies","E":" Visualize","F":"","CorrectOption":"E"},{"QN":"2","Type":"MCQ","Question":"How many requirements are in all released before 30-Jan-20?","A":"44","B":"35","C":"32","D":"25","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D"},{"QN":"3","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Who amongst the below mentioned AgileWaters Trainers & Coaches is CERTIFIED Kanban as well as SAFe Trainer? (Hint 1st Page)","A":" Jeff Lopez (US & India","B":" Vijay Wade (Asia ,Europe & USA)","C":" Edson Fonsceca (Mexico)","D":" Mandar (USA)","E":" Amogh (UK)","F":"","CorrectOption":"B"},{"QN":"4","Type":"MCQ","Question":"How many requirements/tickets are in Design on 15-Jan?","A":"3","B":"17","C":"27","D":"37","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A"},{"QN":"5","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What statement below is correct about PULL?","A":" I only assign work when there is capacity","B":" If there is more inflow I increase capacity as and when required","C":" I don’t PUSH tickets/requirements to next level","D":" I don’t have WIP Limit","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A"},{"QN":"6","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is the Full Form of CFD?","A":" Cumulative Frequency Diagram","B":" Cumulative Flow Diagram","C":" Cross Frequency Diagram","D":" Current Frequency Diagram","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B"},{"QN":"7","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is the benefit of managing flow?","A":" reduction in throughput","B":" More & more Resource utilisation","C":" Flow gets smoother over time","D":" We can handle more work in parallel","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"C"},{"QN":"8","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is Class of Service?","A":" prioritization of work types","B":" a set of policy applying to a category of work","C":" a sonic screwdriver","D":" an contractual obligation made to the customer","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B"},{"QN":"9","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What issue you can make out from above CFD of Kanban system?","A":" PULL mechanism is not implemented (not visible)","B":" PUSH mechanism is implemented.","C":" WIP not implemented.","D":" Bottlenecks are not experienced.","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A"},{"QN":"10","Type":"MCQ","Question":"How does Kanban use evolutionary change?","A":" Enables us to make big changes quickly","B":" Helps us install a pre-designed Kanban process.","C":" Uses understanding and agreement, based on respect","D":" Encourages big bang changes","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"C"},{"QN":"11","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is Feedback Loop in the Kanban Method?","A":" Kanban Meeting and Board","B":" Refinement meeting","C":" Kanban Board Tickets","D":" Class of Service","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A"},{"QN":"12","Type":"MCQ","Question":"On any given day – what is the minimum difference in Backlog & Released requirements?","A":"4","B":"9","C":"18","D":"25","E":"30","F":"","CorrectOption":"C"},{"QN":"13","Type":"MCQ","Question":"How many requirements are completed on 29-Jan-20?","A":"12","B":"17","C":"25","D":"32","E":"44","F":"","CorrectOption":"D"},{"QN":"14","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Full form of SSSF","A":" Standard Safe Sequence & Frequency","B":" Sequential & Serial Subjective Function","C":" Stop Starting Start Finishing","D":" Suboptimal Solution for Standardized Function","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"C"},{"QN":"15","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Is the Flow Laminar?","A":" Yes","B":"No","C":" Can’t say from given data","D":"","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B"},{"QN":"16","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What all Certifications are provided by AgileWaters Consulting under Kanban? (1. TKP,2-KMP1(Kanban System Design), 3-KMP2 – Kanban Management Professional, 4. KP- Kanban Practitioner)","A":" 1 & 2","B":" 2 & 3","C":" 1, 2 & 3","D":" 1 & 4","E":" Non of the above","F":"","CorrectOption":"C"},{"QN":"17","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is the Release frequency in above graph?","A":" Daily","B":" Weekly","C":" Fortnightly","D":" Monthly","E":" None of the above","F":"","CorrectOption":"C"},{"QN":"18","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Reduction in batch size increases Flow","A":" True","B":" Always True","C":" Mostly","D":" False","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"C"},{"QN":"19","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Which of the following statement is TRUE about requirements in Coding?","A":" There are less requirements in coding on 15-Jan than 22-Jan.","B":" There are more requirements on 15-Jan than 22-Jan.","C":" There are equal requirements on 15-Jan & 22-Jan.","D":" Above statements can’t be justified from given data.","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D"},{"QN":"20","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is the frequency of Backlog replenishment (Update)?","A":" Daily","B":" Weekly","C":" Fortnightly","D":" Monthly","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B"},{"QN":"21","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is the end measurement point of System Lead time?","A":" column where work gets delivered to customer","B":" last unbounded queue","C":" first unbounded queue","D":" deployment column","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"C"},{"QN":"22","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is flow efficiency?","A":" effort spent on item","B":" Ratio of time work is actually in progress vs. waiting","C":" Time spent waiting in queues","D":" a key metric of flow","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D"},{"QN":"23","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is Class of Service?","A":" prioritization of work types","B":" a set of policy applying to a category of work","C":" a sonic screwdriver","D":" an contractual obligation made to the customer","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B"},{"QN":"24","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is Feedback Loop in the Kanban Method?","A":" Kanban Meeting and Board","B":" Prioritization meeting","C":" Flow metrics","D":" Service Delivery Review","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A"},{"QN":"25","Type":"MSQ","Question":"What is the benefit of managing flow?","A":" More throughput","B":" Better predictability","C":" Flow gets smoother over time","D":" We can handle more work in parallel","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B C"},{"QN":"26","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is the essence of Kanban in Action?","A":" Deliver faster!","B":" Provoking conversation that leads to change","C":" Having an elaborate board with all information present","D":" Empower teams","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B"},{"QN":"27","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is 2-phase commitment( or de-coupled commitment)?","A":" Can replenish and deliver at different frequencies","B":" Commitment point and the delivery point are not connected","C":" We can reverse our commitment on items we have started","D":" We have more than one commitment and delivery points","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A"},{"QN":"28","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What does this mean: \"SLA expectation of 105 days with 98% on-time\"","A":" The customer should not expect to get anything delivered.","B":" We deliver everything in 98% of 105 days","C":" We have estimated that we can deliver 98% within 105 days.","D":" We promise to deliver within 105 days. We are 98% confident.","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D"},{"QN":"29","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is Capacity Allocation?","A":" Gives guidance where to spent which share of time and energy","B":" Allocates capacity to team members","C":" Policy re share of capability allotted to a category of work","D":" Tells us who is paying which part of the budget","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A"},{"QN":"30","Type":"MCQ","Question":"How does Kanban use evolutionary change?","A":" Enables us to make big changes quickly","B":" Helps us install a pre-designed Kanban process.","C":" Uses understanding and agreement, based on respect","D":" Encourages small deliberate changes","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"C"},{"QN":""}]